skatehut.co.uk 2018-09-02

# Privacy Policy | Skatehut

**SkateHut are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We work to keep our policies in line with the latest legislation. (GDPR)**

**What information do we collect?**

We do not collect personal information from our users, unless that information is necessary,

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, we may collect the following information:

  * Information submitted in forms i.e. name, email address, mailing address, contact number
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of correspondence
  * Details of transactions through our site and of the fulfilment of your orders
  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, resources accessed, behaviours and patterns or otherwise.

You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalise your experience onsite (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

  * To produce targeted, relevant and personalised adverts on external platforms such as Facebook & Instagram

  * To measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others

  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

  * To process transactions and deliver your goods

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

  * To contact you periodically via a number of methods

If you have given us the consent to do so, we may contact you by telephone, email, SMS and post notifying you of products or special offers that may be on interest to you.    

 Please note that some emails from 3rd parties are transactional emails and are part of the overall order process. These include review request emails from Feefo, and post-purchase "Thank You" emails from Bronto. If you have opted out of receiving our newsletter emails (which should be the default option duing our checkout process) then you will not receive any sale offer or other marketing emails from us.

The data you provide will be used for the purpose stated at the time of collection i.e. for the fulfilment of your order should you need to be contacted with regards to an unforeseen issue or for newsletters if you have chosen to receive these when you placed your order or signed up via the form on our website footer.

In all of our communication to you we will offer you the option to opt-in or opt-out.

In the event that you do not wish to be contacted for such purposes, please ensure that you do not tick the appropriate box as you go through the registration or checkout process. You may unsubscribe from our contact list at any time by logging into your account to update your marketing preferences, or click the unsubscribe link that can be found in the footer or any of our marketing emails.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorised with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes; Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone.

This Website uses cookies by the following third parties:

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Google Analytics: This cookie allows us to monitor user interaction with this Website including, but not limited to page views, source and time spent on Website. The information is depersonalised and is displayed as numbers, meaning it cannot be tracked back to individuals. This will help to protect your privacy. Using Google Analytics we can see what content is popular on our Website, and strive to provide you with a better user experience.

Google AdWords: Using Google AdWords code we are able to see which adverts helped lead to a purchase. This allows us to make better use of our paid search budget. This information is not personally identifiable.

DoubleClick: We use remarketing codes to log when users view specific pages, allowing us to provide targeted advertising in the future.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

SkateHut may retain customer personal data for periods of time for legal, audit and compliance purposes and to the extent required by Applicable Laws, for such period as required by Applicable laws. SkateHut shall ensure the confidentiality of all such customer personal data is only retained and processed as necessary for the purpose specified (legal, audit or compliance).

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.skatehut.co.uk

Unit 2, Block 2, Shenstone Trading Estate

Halesowen, West Midlands B63 3XB

sales@skatehut.co.uk
